[BILLY] Do you know what caused the fire?
[CLERK] No one knows, miss.
All I heard was that Mariela survived.
And so did her youngest daughter.
But her eldest daughter died.
[JORDAN] When did the fire happen?
[CLERK] About 12 to 13 years ago, I think.
[BILLY] But the father
wasn't with them?
[CLERK]
No, he wasn't.
The rumor is that
Mariela's husband left her.
[MARIELA SCREAMING]
Ma.
Ma?
I'm here, Ma.
- Hmm?
- As long as your father
and his mistress are together
with that Billy and her little brother,
those bastard children…
I will never be okay.
Billy, please. I need more time with him.
It's already more than enough that
you were given the chance
to spend time with Oliver.
I know my brother will be hurt
when he finds out that
I stopped you from seeing him.
Inhale, exhale, Peter.
Just do what I asked, okay?
Hack into LoveLine ASAP.
- Clear?
- Yes.
I'm working on it.
[BEA] You better be.
Because if you don't do it,
your photos will go viral.
I'm telling you.
Sorry, chief. Sir Peter's here.
Huh? You didn't tell me
he was coming today.
He just suddenly arrived.
I thought you were expecting him.
Hi!
- Peter!
- Hi!
Sorry, I wasn't expecting you.
Hi. Yeah…
Now, I expect you to fulfill
your end of the deal.
Delete those photos.
[BEA] You know, Peter,
our deal was simple.
Once LoveList is completely ruined,
that's when I'll delete all the pictures.
Okay? Thank you.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
- [VALERIE] Billy? We have a problem.
- [BILLY] Yes?
Someone posted this,
and it's getting traction.
"Your secret's not safe with LoveList."
"Confidential LoveLine conversations
and member information leaked."
Why does the message say that?
What's going on?
[BILLY] Hello?
Jordan.
[DISTANT BIRDS CHIRPING]
Someone definitely tried
to leak the files.
Tough luck for them,
all of our confidential data is encrypted.
And we have a second layer of protection,
so if anyone tries to hack,
leak our files,
this will pop up.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[EXHALES] Okay, good.
But, dude, how did they obtain our data?
Good thing you went ahead
with the security measures.
Well, you hired
a great cybersecurity group.
So, your investment paid off.
Besides, you were the one
who reminded me, right?
To protect our secrets.
I'm curious how they slipped
under our noses.
I checked with security,
and no one got in that we didn't know.
Do you think it was Bea again?
Caloy is in prison, isn't he?
So who would she send this time
to gain access to our computers?
[MUSIC BUILDING UP]
[KEYBOARD CLACKING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
- [MUSIC FADING]
- [TRAFFIC NOISE]
[BEA] What the heck is that?
Explain this!
What are you talking about?
"What are you talking about"?
See for yourself!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [COMPUTER WHIRRING]
- Look, that's a virus!
Just look! Your files are corrupted!
No, it's encrypted.
Huh? What the heck do you mean?
Encrypted!
Meaning their data is protected!
That's why all the text
looks scrambled like that,
so that no one can read it.
No one can leak or spread
confidential information
about their clients.
[BEA INHALES SHARPLY, GROANS]
So you mean it's useless?
Yeah. Only an authorized
user can decode it.
Look,
there's not much we can do here.
But I did my part,
so please delete the photos.
[SCOFFS]
I don't think so. Not yet.
What?! Are you kidding me?
This is not what we talked about!
You said steal the files
and you'll delete the photos!
And that's what I did!
- [SCOFFS]
- [BREATHING HEAVILY]
What, are you going to hit me?
Go! Go ahead. Hit me.
Come on, hit me.
Do it. Hit me, Peter.
Want me to make a scene?
Look around.
We've got their attention.
- Hmm?
- [BREATHES HEAVILY]
Go on, hit me.
- [SIGHING DEEPLY]
- [MUSIC SWELLING]
[MUSIC FADES]
You really think you scare me, Peter?
Hmm?
If I were you…
I would behave.
Okay?
You need to behave,
or else
they will find out about you.
And I mean everybody.
[SINISTER MUSIC PLAYING]
Hmm?
Be a good boy, okay?
Peter.
I'm not done with you yet.
So if I call you,
you'd better answer right away.
Okay?
Yes?
Yes.
[SINISTER MUSIC CONTINUES]
[LAPTOP SLAMS SHUT]
[GROANS]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
Marj found out that Peter is staying here.
He made some posts tagging this location,
Summit Bay Hotel.
Then suddenly, those posts disappeared.
That's a bit weird, isn't it?
So, wait. You think it's really him?
Dude, he invested 30 million in us.
It makes no sense if he actually
wants the company to fail.
We are here to ask a few questions, and…
Let's see what happens.
Peter.
- Billy.
- Hi.
- Jordan.
Hi.
What brings you here?
Um…
Someone tried to leak
our confidential data.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Confidential data?
[BILLY] Yes.
Transcript of LoveLine calls,
along with other sensitive information
about our members.
But fortunately,
we have upgraded
our cybersecurity systems,
so we are good.
T-That's good.
Should I be worried?
No.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC FADES]
You were at the office yesterday, and--
And we…
we just wanted to be
transparent with you, Peter.
- Uh, that's why we're here.
- Right.
To inform you about the attempted leak
before you hear about it
from someone else.
We want you to hear from us first.
- Right, right.
- [JORDAN] Right?
And as you can see,
our security measures are all in place,
so nothing to worry about.
Thank you. I… I appreciate that.
- [PHONE RINGING]
- Thanks. Thanks.
I…
Listen. I-I gotta go.
[RINGING CONTINUES]
[BILLY] Okay.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
What?!
What did you tell them?
Nothing! I swear!
I warn you, Peter. Okay?
If you talk, I will ruin your life!
Mark my words!
Okay, okay.
Look, I'll talk to you later.
I have business to attend to.
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Sorry, I cut you off.
I couldn't let you confront him
with just a hunch.
[BILLY] It's okay.
I was just going to ask him.
But did you see it too?
He was acting strange.
Yeah.
But that's not enough.
[MUSIC BECOMES DRAMATIC]
What if you're wrong?
We're going to lose an investor.
What if I'm right?
Yes, you're probably right.
But first, we need proof.
Okay.
[MUSIC INTENSIFYING]
[MUSIC FADES]
[DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
[DARK MUSIC CONTINUES]
[WOMAN] What the hell?!
The road is so wide!
Stop blocking the way!
- I'm just over here on the side!
- Ugh! Don't you have eyes?!
Stop! Just get out of here!
[DARK MUSIC CONTINUES]
Is Papa not coming home?
Isn't he joining us?
You are so dumb, aren't you?
You're stupid!
You really take after your father.
You're both useless!
So, what?
Are you going to take his side?
Then get out of here and go with him!
You deserve each other anyway!
Ma! Ma!
- Take her.
- Ma.
- Help her.
- Help! Ma.
Ma, wake up! Ma!
Ma!
[DARK MUSIC CONTINUES]
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
[MUSIC STOPS]
[DOOR SHUTS]
Ma?
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[LINE RINGING]
[BUSY SIGNAL]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC STOPS]
I'm trying to trace the activity
on the workstation
where Peter was sitting.
So we can find out when
and what time the files were downloaded.
But we still need to find out
if he was really
the one who leaked the files online.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Hey.
Remember, something like this
happened before.
And we caught Caloy.
We'll catch this guy too.
Okay?
Okay.
I'm heading home.
See you tomorrow, dude.
See you.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
Thank you.
Good luck!
- Bye, Billy!
- Good night!
- Thank you!
- Take care.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
Boss.
Why don't you just tell her how you feel?
Now's really not the time
to mess with her head.
I'm just waiting for the right time.
I think, boss, for now,
it's better if you just let her know that
you'll always be there for her.
Okay.
Yeah? [CHUCKLES]
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
Oh, let's get back to work.
- Yeah.
- Okay, sorry.
Boss, aren't you gonna help?
["SANDAL" BY JAMES REID PLAYING]
["SANDAL" CONTINUES]
[MUSIC FADES]
Billy, go to sleep.
Just leave that for tomorrow.
My God, Auntie. We almost lost everything.
Imagine if those files had leaked.
LoveList would've been ruined again.
Was it Bea again?
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
It's possible, Auntie.
But one of our other suspects
is our investor.
But I'm wondering,
why would he want to ruin LoveList
when he invested in it himself?
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
You know what?
You should ask the police for help.
Go ahead. Have them investigate it.
Yes, Auntie.
Jordan's just trying to find
where the files were uploaded
so when we go there, we'll have evidence.
[PRECIOUS] Okay.
Anyway, go to sleep, okay?
- Thank you.
- Okay.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
You're going to see your eldest?
I'll ask her for a favor.
I'll see if she'll give me
a little more time.
After all, I don't have
much time left here anyway.
Maybe she'll…
You're going to tell her
about your illness
so she'll feel sorry for you?
Maybe she'll understand me.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC FADES]
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
[DOOR OPENS]
Mariela?
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
They already checked the bars
in the kitchen.
But it's bad news.
The metal is still sturdy.
[VALERIE] Why can't you just
be honest with her?
Do yourself a favor
and talk to Billy.
And tell her
how much you love her.
Please. Leave us alone.
If it had happened to you,
you'd be angry too.
What's your real problem
with me and my daughter?
[MARIELA]
This should've been ours.
So we won't stop
until we get what's rightfully ours!
[BOTH GRUNTING]
- [THWACKS]
- [MARIELA GRUNTS]
Ma.
Where have you been?
You weren't answering my calls.
Our problem's over.
- Wake up, Oliver.
- Billy?
[WOMAN] Do you think
there are still people inside?
[BILLY BREATHING HEAVILY]
- [JORDAN] Billy!
- [BILLY] Help!